...of a smiley-face sticker
on your homework.
(Jimmy:)- It sounded like a big deal.
- Oh, good Lord.
Are we gonna stand here and listen
to him tear Leonard apart like this?
- Hey, I won a Newcomb medal too.
- My point.
You should've seen this guy
back in the day. Huh?
(Jimmy:)He was so little,
he could fit anywhere.
(Jimmy:)Lockers, trash cans.
(Jimmy:)Oh, man,
how did you get inside that backpack?
(Leonard:)Oh, I can't take all the credit.
You helped a lot.
(Jimmy:)- We were practically a comedy team.
- Like the Black Death in Europe.
(Leonard:)Jimmy, I'm kind of curious
why you wanted to see me.
(Jimmy:)Okay, here it is.
I have this great money-making idea.
I need a gear-head
to get it to the finish line.
Mm, technically, Howard's the gear-head.
Leonard's just a dime-store laser jockey.
(Leonard:)What's the idea?
- This is just between us, right?
- Right.
(Jimmy:)Okay. What do you think about a pair of
glasses that makes any movie into 3D?